VLADIMIR KOCHOSKI

GRAPHIC DESIGNER, VISUAL DESIGNER





+389-78-328-950



vladimirkocoski10@gmail.com



Bitola, North Macedonia

PROFILE

I am a graphic designer with two years of experience. I graduated academy for graphic design Semos in Skopje, but in addition i want to upgrade myself in other fields related to IT. I have strong creative and analytical skills and i am a team player.

SKILLS

- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Power Point
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe InDesign

WORK EXPERIENCE

WAITER

Vino Bar Bure

2017 - 2017

WAITER

Bones Vibes

2018 - 2018

EDUCATION

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

"SOTU" - Gjorgi Naumov - Bitola 2015 - 2019

ASSOCIATE GRAPHIC DESIGN

Semos Academy - Skopje 2019 - 2020

FREELANCE

Graphic Design, Visual Design 2019 - 2022

LANGUAGES

Macedonian

German

Serbian

English